goldbex.com 2019-06-14

# Goldbex - Privacy policy | Goldbex

1\. Protection of personal details

Babyloon International Ltd. informs users that the details entered in the contact forms, and for contract will be stored in property files belonging to Babyloon International Ltd.

That way Babyloon International Ltd. shows its commitment to not to use its contents for a different purpose for which it is collected. This ensures maximum confidentiality and implements appropriate technical security measures to prevent unauthorized access within current regulations regarding data protection. 

2\. Right of access, rectification and cancellation

The data subject has the right of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition of their data. To exercise these rights, data holders can send a written request by mail to the contact address support@goldbex.com. 

3\. Disclosure of information to third parties

Babyloon International Ltd. agree not to sell or transfer the personal information collected on their web sites to other entities for their use without your approval and giving you the opportunity to exercise your right of cancellation and opposition discussed above. 

4\. External links

If the user opts to leave this webpage through webpage links outside of our company, Babyloon International Ltd. will not be responsible for the privacy practices of such websites or the cookies that they can store on the user's computer. 

5\. Legal issues

Babyloon International Ltd. may dispose of the personal information provided by you without your permission when it is required by law, or in good faith provided that such an action is necessary to investigate or protect guests, visitors or members of Babyloon International Ltd. or goods or property (including this website). 

6\. Changes to the Privacy Policy of this website

Babyloon International Ltd. may make changes to the Privacy Policy of this website. All changes will be made ​​available on this website, to keep users informed.
